<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef Abstract="true" Name="OpenTheWindows.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <modNameReadable>Open The Windows</modNameReadable>
    <modIdentifier>JPT_OpenTheWindows</modIdentifier>
    <linkUrl>https://www.patreon.com/jptrrs</linkUrl>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  <HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef ParentName="OpenTheWindows.UpdateFeatureBase">
    <defName>OpenTheWindows_2_0</defName>
    <assemblyVersion>2.0</assemblyVersion>
    <content>
&lt;b&gt;Your good old windows have been upgraded!&lt;/b&gt; 
|We improved the mod's performance and added some exciting new features:
|img:AutoVent|caption:&lt;b&gt;Automatic ventilation:&lt;/b&gt; when this is on, your window will watch the temperature inside. If it gets too hot and the air outside is colder, it will be marked to be opened so your colonists can get some fresh air. On the other hand, if it gets too cold inside, the window will be marked to be closed, keeping the heat in.
|img:Alarm|caption:&lt;b&gt;Close on emergency:&lt;/b&gt; if you&apos;re playing with &lt;i&gt;Better Pawn Control&lt;/i&gt;, you can assign your windows to close whenever the emergency button is on. Very useful reacting to raids!
|Speaking of raids, we also reworked the windows so &lt;b&gt;the AI now sees them as doors when attacking&lt;/b&gt;. This will make the windows even more of a weak spot on your defenses! So if you weren&apos;t already, plan carefully where to place them!
|Finally, this is a treat for those out there who have been supporting the mod community:
|img:SmartWindows|caption:The &lt;b&gt;Smart Window&lt;/b&gt; is an automated solution for all your window needs. They are as strong as reinforced windows but are able to open and close without needing a colonist to operate them, responding instantly to commands issued by you or the new auto-ventilation and emergency features.
|They are &lt;b&gt;not included&lt;/b&gt; with this update, but are available to everyone at my Patreon page. &lt;i&gt;To download it, follow the link above or go to https://www.patreon.com/jptrrs.&lt;/i&gt;
|Enjoy!
	</content>
  </HugsLib.UpdateFeatureDef>

  
</Defs>